[
	{
		"id": 0,
		"question": "Frontend",
		"correct": 0,
		"options": [
			"The code that the user interacts with when visiting a website",
			"The first page you see when visiting a website",
			"The code that handles background stuff",
			"A website that adapts to your screen size"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 1,
		"question": "Backend",
		"correct": 1,
		"options": [
			"A programming base to start off",
			"The code that handles background stuff",
			"A place to store secured information",
			"The code that the user interacts with when visiting a website"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 2,
		"question": "Framework",
		"correct": 2,
		"options": [
			"The code that handles background stuff",
			"The code that the user interacts with when visiting a website",
			"A programming base to start off",
			"A way to track all code changes overtime"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 3,
		"question": "Version control",
		"correct": 3,
		"options": [
			"A place to store secured information",
			"Giving your website a version",
			"Where you code your website",
			"A way to track all code changes overtime"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 4,
		"question": "IDE",
		"correct": 0,
		"options": [
			"Where you code your website",
			"A way to communicate with different applications",
			"A way to track all code changes overtime",
			"A website where the content dynamically is generated"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 5,
		"question": "SPA",
		"correct": 1,
		"options": [
			"A way to communicate with different applications",
			"A one-page website that load in content as needed",
			"Where you code your website",
			"?14"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 6,
		"question": "API",
		"correct": 2,
		"options": [
			"A one-page website that load in content as needed",
			"A place to store secured information",
			"A way to communicate with different applications",
			"A website where the content dynamically is generated"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 7,
		"question": "SEO",
		"correct": 3,
		"options": [
			"A website where all content is the same for everyone and can only be changed manually",
			"A dynamically is generated website",
			"A website that adapts to your screen size",
			"Optimizng your website for search engines"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 8,
		"question": "Static website",
		"correct": 1,
		"options": [
			"A website that is slow",
			"A website where all content is the same for everyone and can only be changed manually",
			"A one-page website that load in content as needed",
			"A website where the content dynamically is generated"
		]
	},
	{
		"id": 9,
		"question": "Responsive website",
		"correct": 2,
		"options": [
			"A website where the content dynamically is generated",
			"A website that is very fast",
			"A website that adapts to your screen size",
			"A one-page website that load in content as needed"
		]
	}
]